時は戦国、乱世の時代。
からくり人の住むジパング国では群雄割拠して合戦に明け暮れ、
からくり武芸者たちも勝利と栄光を目指してしのぎを削っていた。
そしていま、からくり武芸者ナンバー１を目指す、とてつもないヒーローが誕生した！
ムサシ、見参でござるだス！
からくり剣豪伝ムサシロード
男はいつでも　世界の真ん中で
いちばん　強くなる日を
AH! AH! 夢見て
心の刃　大空にふりかざし
冒険の旅の　幕を開ける
ジパング国を　さすらう剣豪
その名　からくりびと　ムサシ
鍔迫り合いの音が
眩しい人生
戦い　昨日よりも　今日　強い
BUGEI! 二刀流　ムサシ
明日は　輝くぞ
鍔迫り合いの音が
眩しい人生
戦い　思い切りと　静けさと
BUGEI! 二刀流　ムサシ
みけんが　きらめいた　ムサシ！！
에도토피아에 도달한 무사시는 제니가탄에게 잡혀 감옥에 들어가게 되었다.
Musashi finally came to Edotopia, but he was caught by Zenigatan and jailed.
결국엔 무죄를 증명하고, 에도 성에 오로지 달렸지만
His innocence was proven at last and he ran to Edo Castle,
아주 조금 늦어 에도성은 이미 문을 닫고 말았다.
but he was late and Edo Castle's door was already closed.
무사시는 과연 무예 대회에 출전할 수 있을 것인가?
Will Musashi be able to participate in the martial arts competition?
난입! 무예대회
Raid into
the Martial Arts Competition
지팡구 무예대회 회장
Jipangu Martial Arts Competition
Ieyasu
이에야스
드디어! 나야말로 미야모토 마을의 무사시이오!
Finally! I am Musashi, from Miyamoto village!
자, 승부!
A match!
벤케이 등장!
Benkei appears!
미야모토 마을, 수박가르기의 승리이오!
It's the victory of Miyamoto watermelon cut-dasu!
졌다!
I lost!
바이켄! 간다!
Baiken! Here I go!
미야모토 마을, 혼례를 약속하는 승리이오!
It's the victory of the marriage in Miyamoto-dasu!
무사시 씨 멋져요!
Mr. Musashi, you're awesome!
맡겨만 주시오.
Leave it to me-dasu!
여자 앞에 잘 보이려고 하는 네 모습, 꼴사납다!
How unsightly is your ogling!
오, 내 라이벌 코지로! 오늘로 결판을 내소!
Oh, my rival Kojirō! I'll finish you as of today-dasu!
그런 대사를 하기엔 10년은 이르다!
You're 10 years early to say that!
봐라! 필살! 츠바메가에시!
Look! Never miss a foe! Tsubamegaeshi!
어라! UFO이오.
Huh?! It's a UFO-dasu.
어?
Huh?
미야모토 마을, 승려술의 승리이오!
It's the victory of Miyamoto Buddhist monk cut-dasu!
바... 보...
Idi...ot...
승부 끝! 미야모토 마을의 무사시 우승!
Match set! Musashi from Miyamoto won!
이걸로 지팡구 제일이오! 오츠루 씨, 기뻐하시오!
I'm the number one of Jipangu by this-dasu! Otsuru, be happy-dasu!
오츠루 기뻐요!
I'm happy!
무사시 씨, 일어나세요, 무사시 씨!
Mr. Musashi, wake up! Mr. Musashi!
꿈꾸고 있을 때가 아니에요.
It's not the time to be sleeping.
무예 대회에 가야죠?
Aren't you going to the competition?
오츠루 씨...
Otsuru!
그렇소!
Ah, right!
제니가탄 두목, 신세를 졌소.
Boss Zenigatan, I am indebted-dasu.
다녀오겠소.
See you later-dasu.
잠깐 기다려라!
Wait for a moment!
멈춰도 소용없소. 지팡구 제일의 검사로...
No use stopping me-dasu. To become the number one Martial Artist of Jipangu...
어라?
Huh?
칼은 여기 있어요.
The swords are here.
어라, 졌소. 이야...
Heh, I lost-dasu!
시합 앞에 먼저 배를 채워야죠.
Before the competition, you gotta be full first.
이건 대단한 밥이오!
This is an awesome meal-dasu!
내가 무사시 씨를 감옥에 쳐넣은 사죄의 증표입니다.
This is the certificate of apology, for throwing Mr. Musashi into a prison.
이야, 사죄라니, 그런!
Heh, a certificate!
수줍소!
I'm embarassed-dasu!
내가 끈질기게 붙잡다가 접수를 아쉽게 못 하게 되다니, 나쁜 일을 하고 말았습니다.
I am truly sorry for holding you stubbornly and making you fail to register for the competition.
괜찮소. 어떻게든 되겠소. 나, 부탁해 보겠으니...
It's alright-dasu. Something will happen-dasu. I'll ask them-dasu!
어쨌든 힘내서 무예 대회에서 우승하세요!
Anyway, take the championship in the martial arts competition!
잘 먹겠소!
Thank you for the meal!
자! 이걸!
Here! Have this!
이거, 무엇이오?
What's this?
백명의 파워가 녹아있는 강력한 살무사 드링크이오.
It's a viper drink that has the power of 100 people.
사, 살무사드링크?
Vi- vi- viper drink?!
와, 왔다, 왔다, 왔다, 왔소!
It's coming! It came! It came-dasu!
우승을 기원합니다!
I look forward for your victory!
타오르오! 끓어오르오! 폭발하오!
It burns-dasu! It boils-dasu! It explodes-dasu!
멈춰라!
Stop!
나, 서둘러야 하오. 비키시오!
I gotta hurry up-dasu. Move away-dasu!
여긴 제너럴 이에야스 님의 관청이다. 아이가 올 곳이 아니다!
This is the office of General Ieyasu. It's not a place for a kid to come!
아니, 아니오! 나야말로 미야모토 마을의 무예가 무사시오!
No, that's not it! I am Musashi, a Martial Artist from Miyamoto village-dasu!
제너럴 이에야스 님의 지팡구 무예대회에 출전하오! 접수는 어디이오?
I am going to participate in Jipangu Martial Arts Competition of General Ieyasu-dasu! Where do I register-dasu?
뭐가 이상하오!
What's so funny-dasu?!
자, 무예 대회 접수는 어제까지. 이미 대회 1차 예선은 끝났어.
Hey, registration for the martial arts competition was yesterday. The first preliminary contest is already over.
알고 있소. 그래도 나, 어제 접수를 간발의 차로 하지 못했소.
I know-dasu. But I couldn't register yesterday because I was slightly late-dasu!
그럼 내년에 와라. 내년.
Then come again, in next year.
내년까지 기다릴 수 없소!
I can't wait until next year-dasu!
부탁드리오. 10문 드릴 테니.
Please! I'll give you 10 mons-dasu.
뭐라? 설마 쇼군을 위해 일하는 우리에게 매수하겠다는 거냐!
What? Are you trying to bribe us who work for Shogun?
돌아가! 안 돌아가면 경찰을 부르겠다!
Go back! If you don't go back, we'll call the police!
형! 100문 드릴 테니 기분 풀어주시오.
Bro! I'll give you 100 mons, so cheer up-dasu!
뭘 해도 소용없다! 방해니까 당장 여기서 떠나라!
Whatever you do, they are futile! Leave right now!
그런 말 하지 말구... 자! 흉내!
Don't say that... Look! Mimicry!
물구나무서기! 이렇게!
Handstanding! Look!
돌아가랬으면 돌아가!
If we said you to go back, go back!
이제 알겠소! 힘으로라도 시합에 들겠소!
I get it-dasu! I'm going to enter the competition by force-dasu!
뭐라? 쇼군을 거역하면 참수다. 돌아가라!
What? If you defy Shogun, you'll be decapitated. Go back!
참수? 내... 목숨을 건 꿈이...
Decapitated?! My dream that I risked my life for...
나, 이 날을 위해 쓰라린 수련을 받으며, 배가 고픈 것도 참아가며 왔는데...
I endured the hunger and practiced for this day and...
너무하오....
You're cruel-dasu!
시끄럽다! 저 목소리를 어떻게 해라!
That's noisy! Do something with that voice!
뭔 짓이오!
What are you doing-dasu?!
젠장! 기억해두겠소...
Damn! Remember this...
제 5 예선 회장
Fifth Preliminary Contest Place
에도토피아의 7개 곳에 예선장이 배치되어 있고
Preliminary contest places were placed in 7 different areas of Edotopia,
각지에서 모인 무예가들이 실력을 뽐내고 있었다.
and Martial Artists from different places were competing.
제 5 예선 회장
Fifth Preliminary Contest Place
져, 졌습니다!
I- I lost!
승부 끝! 주베 님의 승리!
Match set! Mr. Jūbē wins!
-스님...
-이 예선장에도 없는 모양이구나.
-Master...
-I guess he's not here too.
역시 무사시 씨에게 무슨 일이 일어난 게?
Did something happened to Mr. Musashi at all...?
설마. 예선장은 총 7개. 아직 두 곳이 남아있으니 걱정 마라.
I think not. There are total 7 places. We have two left to check out.
-그럼 다음 회장으로!
-그러자꾸나. 다음엔 분명 있을 거다.
-Then, to the next place!
-Let's do so. We'll find him in the next place.
무사시 씨...
Mr. Musashi...
호외! 호외! 제 3 예선 회장에서 코지로가 츠바메가에시로 3명을 쓰러트렸대요!
Extra! Extra! At the third preliminary place, Kojirō took down three people with his Tsubamegaeshi!
-잘생겼어!
-멋지다! 딱 내 취향이야!
-He's so handsome!
-So cool! He's totally my type!
코지로 님!
Mr. Kojirō!
코지로...?
Kojirō!
물귀신이다!
It's a Kappa!
물귀신 따위 아니오.
I'm not a Kappa-dasu.
제 1회 무예 대회에서 츠바메가에시로 필살을 써 모든 것을 뚫고 등장한 건
The one who appeared in the first martial arts competition by going through with Tsubamegaeshi is...
천재 검사, 코지로...
a genius Martial Artist, Kojirō...
비검! 츠바메가에시!
Secret sword! Tsubamegaeshi!
멋져! 코지로 님!
So cool! Mr. Kojirō!
우승 후보 중 하나로 유망하고, 특히 에도토피아의 여성에게 인기는 제일이다.
He is one of the promising champion candidates, and he is popular among the girls in Edotopia.
그 꼴사나운 멋진 척 하는 놈이 우승 후보라니, 뭔가 잘못됐소!
Something must be wrong, to call that unsightly bastard-dasu!
봐봐, 봐봐! 꼴사나워!
Look, look! How silly!
얼굴도 표정도 촌스러워!
His face and look are all uncool!
시끄럽소!
Shut up-dasu!
~소? 촌스러워!
dasu? Uncool!
이 이상 모욕은 용서할 수 없소! 궁디팡팡이오!
I won't forgive any more insult-dasu! I'll spank you-dasu!
역시 바보야!
He's an idiot after all!
이제 됐소...
This is enough-dasu...
Sixth Preliminary Contest Place
제 6 예선 회장
어라, 이런 곳에도 작은 성이 있었소.
Huh, there's a small castle in this place too-dasu.
역시 에도토피아오...
This is what Edotopia is like-dasu...
저, 이 성에는 누가 사오?
Uh, who lives in this castle-dasu?
뭔 소리냐! 여긴 지팡구 무예 대회 예선 대회장의 하나다!
What are you talking about? This is one of the preliminary place of Jipangu Martial Arts Competition!
아, 마침 잘 됐소!
Oh, that's good to know-dasu!
잠깐, 잠깐, 어딜 가나!
Hey, hey, where are you going to?
당연하오! 나, 무예 대회에 출전하오.
It's obvious-dasu! I go out for the martial arts competition-dasu.
그럼 참가증을 보여라.
Then show me the voucher.
참가증? 그거, 무엇이오?
Voucher? What's that-dasu?
어제 접수에서 참가 신청할 때 받았을 터다!
You should received one in the registration!
접수... 아! 그렇소.
In the registration... Ah, right-dasu!
어라? 이상하오. 분명 여관에 두고 온 듯 하오...
Huh? Something's not right-dasu. I must've left in the inn-dasu.
그럼 가져오면 되겠구나.
Then go take it.
저기, 저기. 어떻게든 들여보내 주시면 좋겠소. 시간이 없소.
Hey, I'd like you to let me go inside no matter what-dasu. There is no time-dasu.
뭐, 확실히 시합은 이미 시작했지만...
Well, the competition already began...
저기, 어떻게든 들여보내 주시오.
I'd like you to let me go insisde-dasu.
알겠다. 명부를 보지. 이름은?
Alright. Let me see the roster. What's your name?
미야모토 마을의 무사시... 가 아니라, 저...
Musashi from Miyamoto village... no, um...
코지로이오!
I am Kojirō-dasu!
코지로 님은... 제 3 회장이다.
Mr. Kojirō will go to the third contest place.
여기가 아니다.
Not here.
아, 미안하오. 바이켄이오.
Ah, I'm sorry-dasu. It's Baiken-dasu.
바이켄 님? 그럼 분명 아까 전부터 계속 시합 중이다!
Mr. Baiken? He is already having a match inside!
틀렸소.
This is bad-dasu.
아까부터 타인의 이름을 도용하는 수상한 놈이다!
A suspicious guy that impersonate another person's name!
그, 그런! 나, 나...
N- no, I, I...
무예 대회를 방해하는 무뢰한!
A malcontent that interrupts the martial arts competition!
잡아라!
Get him!
아니, 아니, 그만두소! 난 아무 나쁜 짓도 하지 않았소!
N- no, stop it-dasu! I didn't do anything wrong-dasu!
문답무용! 저항하면 베어버린다!
No questions accepted! Resist and be cut!
그래!
Right!
가만있지 않겠소!
[?] I will not stand still-dasu!
기다리시오!
Wait for me!
제니가탄 두목.
Boss Zenigatan!
이 멍청이가. 멋대로 싸우지 말했지!
You idiot! I told you not to fight with random people!
뭔 짓이오!
What are you doing-dasu?!
이 자는 내가 최근 고용한 자로 절대 수상한 자가 아닙니다.
This guy is the one I recently hired, and definitely isn't someone suspicious.
네 부하라는 말인가.
Are you saying that he's  under your order?
예. 이 실례는 마음 넓게 용서를 구하외다. 여하튼 첩첩산중에서 막 온 놈이라서!
Right. Please excuse him with your generous mind. He just came from the heart of the mountains after all!
알겠소. 그러나 조심하시오.
Alright. But be careful.
자! 가라! 어서! 회장 정리를 도와라.
Now, go! Quick! Help tidying up the place!
그럼 인사는 나중에.
I'll introduce him later.
미야모토 마을의 무사시... 눈에 거슬리니 한조 님의 부하에게 알리자!
Musashi from Miyamoto village... Let's go tell Hanzō's subordinates!
과연 무사시는 무예 대회에 나갈 수 있을까? 질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
Will Musashi be able to compete in the martial arts competition? Wait for the stormy latter half!
카라쿠리 검호전 무사시 로드
Karakuri Kengouden: Musashi Road
어떻게든 된 것 같군.
I guess we went through.
아까 갑자기 때린 것, 이해해 주쇼.
Please understand that I had to hit you moments ago.
아니오. 그래도 놀랐소.
It's alright. But I was surprised-dasu!
혹시 뭐가 잘못되어서 만일 반역자로 지목되면 한조 님의 부하에게 쏘아질 수 있으니...
If something goes wrong and you are pointed out as a traitor, you might get shot by Hanzō's underlings...
한조?
Hanzō?
도깨비같은 두목으로, 에도 성의 경비를 맡는 이하 닌자 그룹의 수장이다.
He is a monster-like chief of Iga Ninja Force that guards Edo Castle.
이 회장에도, 저기!
In this place too. Look!
저기에도.
There too.
저게 한조의 부하이오?
Are they Hanzō's underlings-dasu?
그들은 조금이라도 수상한 인간을 발견하면 용서없이 처치해요.
When they find anyone suspicious, they get rid of one right away.
그러니까 조심하세요.
So be careful.
알겠소.
Got it-dasu.
어떻게든 참가할 수 있기를 내가 빌어 줄 테니까.
I'll wish you to be able to participate in the competition!
여기 있어 주세요.
Please stay here.
한조라고 하면...
Hanzō must be...
막부를 쓰러뜨리겠다는 나쁜 놈이오.
a bad guy who's trying to take down shogunate.
나, 주베 씨에게 알려야겠다고 생각했소.
I did thought I should tell this to Mr. Jūbē.
안되오! 나, 무예 대회에 온 것이오!
No-dasu! I came to the martial arts competition!
이제 점심시간입니다! 오후에는 준준결승을 하겠습니다!
Lunch time begins now. Semi-semi-finals will begin in afternoon.
바이켄
Baiken
고자에몽
Gozaemon
상위 8명이오... 이렇게 되면 어떻게든...
So it's best eight-dasu... From now on anything goes.
비밀 작전이 번뜩였소!
I got a secret plan-dasu!
여기에도 없었네요. 무사시 씨 무슨 일일까요?
He's not here too. I wonder what happened to Mr. Musashi...
여기가 아니었나 보구나. 아직 마지막 예선장이 남아 있어. 낙심하지 마라.
I guess it wasn't here either. We still have the last place left. Don't be disheartened.
네.
Yes.
이곳은 무예 대회 참가자의 대기실이다.
This is the waiting room for participants for the competition.
여긴 관계자 이외 출입 금지다.
Non-personnel are not allowed to enter!
나, 도시락 배달하러 왔소.
I am here to deliver lunch box-dasu.
도시락? 그런 이야기는 들은 적 없다!
Lunch box? Nobody told me about this.
그래도 정말이오.
But this is true-dasu.
부탁한 자의 이름은?
Who asked for it?
지나갑니다!
E- excuse me!
아, 저 사람이오! 잠깐, 잠깐!
Ah, ah, there he is-dasu! Hey, you!
알았으니 잠깐 기다려!
Hey, just a moment!
들어가도 괜찮소?
Can I go in-dasu?
좋다. 빨리 나와라.
Right. Come back as soon as possible.
예, 실례하겠소!
Alright, thank you all the time-dasu!
누구냐!
Who are you?!
수상한 자는 아니오. 사무라이 씨에게 드리는 선물이오.
I'm not someone suspicious-dasu. I have a present for Mr. Samurai-dasu!
뭐라? 선물?
What? A present?
그렇소. 예쁜 아가씨로부터의 선물이오.
Right-dasu! A present from a pretty girl-dasu!
무, 뭐?!
Wh- what?!
사무라이 씨도 얄밉소. 이 미남!
How wonderful are you, you lady-killer!
그렇구나. 역시!
Heh, I see, of course!
자, 빨리 열어보자!
Open this right away!
알겠소.
Alright-dasu.
뭘까...
What could it be...
아팠소? 미안하오.
Did it hurt-dasu? I'm sorry-dasu.
시합이 끝날 때까지 움직이지 말아 주시오.
Please don't move until the competition ends-dasu.
이제 준준결승전을 행하겠습니다!
Time for the semi-semi-finals!
준준결승전 시합은 나루토 우주시오 류, 하치스카돈베.
Semi-semi-final match will be between Whirling Tides of Maelstrom style, Hachisukadonbe,
대하는 자는 한바 사사야마 류, 고자에몽!
and his competitor, Hanba Sasayama style, Gozaemon!
그렇소!
That's right-dasu!
고자에몽 님, 그 마스크는 뭡니까?
Mr. Gozaemon, what's with that mask?
아, 급히 어지러워서...
Oh, I suddenly feel dizzy...
그렇게는 진정한 시합은 무리가...
Wouldn't it be difficult to have a true math?
아, 아니오. 괜찮소.
N- no, it'll be alright-dasu!
이렇소!
As you see-dasu!
그럼 나오시오!
Then come out!
단번승부!
Only one match!
시작!
Start!
바이켄 님, 여기서 결승전을 하겠소!
Mr. Baiken, we'll have the final match here-dasu!
그러니까 어떻게든 이기겠소!
So no matter what, I'll win-dasu!
가져가겠소!
Chance!
저 자세... 게다가 움직임도 닮았는데... 그래도 설마...
That posture... and movement reminds me... but still...
역시 상위 8... 간단하게 이겨지지 않소!
That's best 8... He's not going down so easily!
필살! 나루토의 소용돌이!
Special move! Whirling Tides of Maelstrom!
뭣이오?
What-dasu?
이대로는 눈이 돌아가 지고 마오.
In this rate, I'm going to be dizzy and lose-dasu...
무의미한 짓이다!
Futile attempt!
이걸 어쩌오.
What should I do-dasu...
눈이 돌아가기 시작했소...
I started to become dizzy-dasu...
이것이오!
That's it-dasu!
찌르기!
Thrust!
져, 졌다!
I lost!
승부, 거기까지! 고자에몽 님의 승리!
Match set! Mr. Gozaemon wins!
해냈소! 이야!
I did-dasu! Yay!
고맙소!
Thank you!
나, 무사시이지만... 복잡한 기분이오...
My name is Musashi-dasu, but... it feels complicated-dasu.
음... 꽤 하는 판단력이군, 고자에몽 님.
That's some judgment, Mr. Gozaemon.
준준결승전 시합은 쿠사리가마류 바이켄!
Semi-semi-finals will feature Kusarigama style Baiken,
상대하는 자는 공포파괴류 스즈키 시게노신!
The competitor is Fear Destroy style, Suzuki Shigenoshin!
형! 힘내!
Brother! Do your best!
거기가지! 바이켄 님의 승리!
Stop! Mr. Baiken wins!
역시 형!
That's our brother!
고, 고자에몽 님!
M- Mr. Gozaemon!
곧 제 6 예선 회장에서 결승전이 시작됩니다!
Finals will begin soon in the sixth preliminary place!
바이켄
고자에몬
Baiken
Gozaemon
Victory
우승
더구나, 이 시합의 승자는 본년도 상위 7명의 카라쿠리 무예가로서 제너럴 이에야스 님의 결승 어전 시합에 출전할 수 있습니다.
Moreover, the winner in this match can go to the final match
in the presence of General Ieyasu as the top 7 Karakuri Martial Artists.
누가 이겨도 좋은 기억이 남을 것이오.
Whoever wins, it will become one of the good memories.
시작!
Start!
역시 저 자세는 무사시!
Judging on that posture, he is Musashi!
무사시! 왜 그랬냐!
Musashi! Why did you do this?
찌르기!
Piercing!
역시 무사시 맞구나!
You are Musashi!
그 자는 가짜이오!
That guy is a fake!
그 자는 비겁하게 몰래 들어와 행패를 부려 기절시켜 소생 흉내를 낸 가짜 무예가이오!
That guy cowardly sneaked in, play havoc to make me faint, and assumed my identity! He is a fake Martial Artist!
뭐라? 그런 것인가!
What? Is that true?
쇼군께서 결재하신 신성한 무예 대회에 훼방을 놓는 반역자이오!
He's a traitor for hindering the sacred martial arts competition Shogun approved!
잡아서 처형해 주쇼!
Get him and execute him!
예!
Right!
기다리쇼!
Wait!
누구든간에 제너럴 이에야스 님의 어전 시합 출전을 정하는 결승전. 결판을 내겠소!
Whoever he is, this is the match that will decide the participation
to the final match in the presence of General Ieyasu! I will finish this!
예. 알겠소이다. 바이켄 님 말씀대로 한다면, 일단 물러서시오!
Alright, as you wish. To do as Mr. Baiken said, step back for now!
바이켄...
Baiken...
가자, 무사시!
Here it goes, Musashi!
건방지다!
How impertinent!
건너편 비상구로 탈출해라.
Escape using the emergency exit on the other side.
바이켄... 그렇게는 성가실...
Baiken... that will bother...
괜찮아! 가라!
It's allright! Go!
이 극악한 가짜 무예가 놈! 잘 알아둬라!
You heinous impostor Martial Artist! Realize this!
비상구
EXIT
승부 끝! 바이켄 님의 승리!
Match set! Mr. Baiken wins!
역시 바이켄 님!
As expected from Mr. Baiken!
그 사내는 어쨌나!
Where did that man go?!
비상구
EXIT
없다! 잡아라!
He isn't there! Get him!
찾았다!
There he is!
만약 날뛰면 베어라!
If he resists, you're good  to cut him!
무사시... 뭔 일이 있는진 모르겠지만 무사하길 빈다.
Musashi... I don't know what happened, but please be safe!
무사시 형 왜 그래?
What happened to Musashi?
괜찮아! 걱정 마라!
It'll be all right! Don't worry!
녀석은 흉악범이다! 어떻게든 잡아서 처형해라!
He is a vicious criminal! Get him no matter what and execute him!
아니오! 나는 나쁜 일을 하지 않았소!
That's wrong-dasu! I didn't do anything wrong-dasu!
단고
DANGO
무사시 씨?
Mr. Musashi?
-무사시-
-비켜라!
-Musashi-
-Move!
그래, 확실히 무사시다. 근데 대체 뭔 일을 했을까...
Yeah, he definitely is Musashi. But I wonder what did he do...
그래도 다행이에요. 무사시 씨 틀림없이 에도토피아에 왔네요!
But it's a relief... Mr. Musashi definitely came to Edotopia!
이 녀석은 무사시.
This is Musashi.
역시 내 손으로 지옥으로 떨어질 운명이었는가.
He was destined to fall to the hell by my hands.
배가 고프오...
I am hungry-dasu...
지팡구 제일의 무예가를 꿈꾸고 있었을 터이던 무사시는
Supposed to be dreaming to be the number one martial artist of Jipangu,
가련하게도 이에야스에게 거스르는 반역자라는 오명을 입고
how miserable - Musashi has gained a dishonor of a traitor that defies Ieyasu,
지명수배의 대악인이 되어 버렸다.
and became a heinous criminal that is wanted.
과연 무사시에게 내일은 있을 것인가?
Will Musashi even have a tomorrow?
カラのポケットに　ツキが
飛び込むことも　あるさ
おっきな声で　笑えば
あしたには　朝が来る
無くすものなんか　何もないさ
やっちゃえ！イケイケ！
手ぶらは　強いぜ
てなもんだ　のーてんきに行こう
人生　てなもんさ　チャンスが　ほら
しっぽを振って　追ってくるぜ
てなもんだ　のーてんきに行こう
未来も　てなもんさ　あしたが　ほら
両手ひろげて　笑ってるぜ
지명수배중인 나는 나쁜 놈들에게 얽혀 있던 귀여운 아이를 구했소.
While being wanted, I rescued a cute child surrounded by bad guys-dasu.
그 아이, 사실은 이에야스의 손녀인 센히메였지만 그걸 몰랐던 나는
That child actually was Senhime who is a granddaughter of Ieyasu, but not knowing that,
무예 대회 회장에 몰래 들어가 주베 님과 싸우게 됐소.
I sneaked into the martial arts competition place and had a match against Mr. Jūbē-dasu.
다음 이야기! 센히메를 구하고 승부이오
Next story! Rescue Senhime and Have a Match
질풍노도의 대활약을 보시오!
Check out the stormy great activity!
다음 이야기
센히메를 구하고 승부이오
기대하세요!
Next Episode
and Have a Match
Rescue Senhime
Look forwards for it!